bluephoenixmedia.com 2017-06-09

# Blue Phoenix Media - Privacy Policy

Last updated October 24, 2006.

This policy applies to Blue Phoenix Media’s collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by Blue Phoenix Media’s on its, (a) websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the "Websites"), (b) on various third party websites, and (c) to Blue Phoenix Media’s other information collection, including the purchase of customer lists from third parties, or the use of customer lists from third parties. Blue Phoenix Media is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third party websites or applications.

BY VISITING THIS WEBSITE AND REQUESTING INFORMATION, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES THERON, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. BLUE PHOENIX MEDIA RESERVES THE RIGHT TO MODIFY THE PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME EFFECTIVE UPON POSTING OF THE MODIFIED AT [www.bluephoenixmedia.com](http://www.bluephoenixmedia.com/). PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES AS IT IS YOUR SOLE RESPONSIBILITY TO BE AWARE OF CHANGES.   
IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO BLUE PHOENIX MEDIA OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEB SITES REFERRED TO IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

**Collection of Survey Information**

Blue Phoenix Media collects information from individuals by various methods, including, but not limited to, when an individual voluntarily completes an Blue Phoenix Media survey, order form, or a registration page either online or offline, or by means of online or offline surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties (collectively, a "Survey"). (As used herein, "online" means using the Internet, including the Websites, and related technologies, and "offline" means by methods other than online, including in person, in the postal mail, using telephones and cell phones, and other similar means.) In the Surveys, Blue Phoenix Media or a third party (a "Third Party") may ask an individual to provide various information to Blue Phoenix Media, which may include his or her name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may requested from time to time (together, "Survey Information"). Completing the Surveys is completely voluntary, and individuals are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to Blue Phoenix Media or Third Party, but an individual may receive incentives from Blue Phoenix Media or a Third Party in exchange for providing Survey Information to Blue Phoenix Media. 

**Collection of Third Party List Information**

Blue Phoenix Media collects information from individuals when an individual provides information to a third party and Blue Phoenix Media subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the third party (the "Seller"). Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, an individual's name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the Seller (together, "Third Party List Information"). When acquiring Third Party List Information, Blue Phoenix Media seeks assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Third Party List Information to Blue Phoenix Media and that the Seller has a right to provide offers from advertisers to the individuals whose personal information is included on the Seller's list. 

**Collection of Other Information.**

Blue Phoenix Media obtains information from individuals include (1) when an individual is making a claim for a prize or seeking to redeem an incentive offered by Blue Phoenix Media or by a third party, (2) when an individual requests assistance through Blue Phoenix Media's customer service department, and (3) when an individual voluntarily subscribes to a Blue Phoenix Media service or newsletter (together, "Other Information"). 

**Cookies, and Web Beacons**

A cookie is a small piece of data which is sent from a web server to a web browser and stored locally on the user's machine. Cookies are used to improve the experience web users have when they see web advertisements. Cookies are not viruses and cannot erase your hard drive or otherwise damage your computer. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information. 

Cookies are used to ensure that when a web user clicks on an ad, they are sent to the correct click-through destination. They are also used by our reporting system to estimate the total reach of an ad campaign, as well as frequency of display. This allows advertisers to determine with greater accuracy the composition of the audience they reach. Cookies are also used to sequence the delivery of a series of ads to a web browser, and to limit the number of times a web browser receives any one advertisement. You can always choose not to receive a cookie file by enabling your Web browser to refuse cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie. 

Used in combination with cookies, a Web beacon is an often-transparent graphic image, usually no larger than 1 x 1 pixel, that is placed on a Web site or in an e-mail that is used to monitor the behavior of the user visiting the Web site or sending the e-mail. When the HTML code for the Web beacon points to a site to retrieve the image, at the same time it can pass along information such as the IP address of the computer that retrieved the image, the time the Web beacon was viewed and for how long, the type of browser that retrieved the image and previously set cookie values.

Blue Phoenix Media currently uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about you with information about you in its database. Additionally, Blue Phoenix Media may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future. 

**Information Sharing:**

Blue Phoenix Media records information about the interactions that include ad content (banner) delivery, counting click-throughs on an ad, and tracking webpage views after a click-through. Browsers typically provide the browser version, the operating system, and the IP address of the computer in use. This non-personally identifiable information is collected from web users to assist in the proper function of our service as well as the targeting of advertisements from our customers and the reporting of aggregate data to both advertisers and publishers.

**Our Partners**

At Blue Phoenix Media, we advertise various sweepstakes and prizes on behalf of our partners and other third-parties. Please note that we are not responsible for prize fulfillment for contests that you enter that are not owned by Blue Phoenix Media. We may from time to time want to include you in our partner’s announcements and promotions. Please contact the advertiser about any issues regarding their offers.

**Data Security**

We will share demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This however will not be linked to any personal information that will make you identifiable. Blue Phoenix Media may use third parties to deliver certain tasks. Only the necessary information will be used in order for them to do their task. 

Blue Phoenix Media uses partners with third-party companies to provide service to you. When you sign up for one of these services, the information you provide will be shared with the third-party and your privacy will be in accordance with that third-parties privacy policy. Blue Phoenix Media will use advertising that will navigate to a partner site and therefore your privacy will then be governed by the privacy policy of that site. 

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites to provide advertisements and services that may be of interest to you.

**Children under 13 years of age**

Blue phoenix Media will never knowingly solicit nor will it accept personally identifiable information from users known to be under thirteen (13) years of age. This policy is to comply with the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) <http://www.coppa.org/comply.htm>.

**Links**
